[       
        {
            "product_id": 1,
            "product_name": "HARRY POTTER & HEGWID",           
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "HPT001001",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/harry-potter/harry-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/harry-potter/harry-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 2,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 2,
            "product_name": "HERMINIONE BALL DRESSHERMINIONE BALL DRESS",
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "HPT001002",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 2,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 3,
            "product_name": "LUNA LOVEGOOD LION MASK",
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "HPT001003",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/harry-potter/luna-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/harry-potter/luna-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 2,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 4,
            "product_name": "SNAPE PATRONUS",           
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "HPT001004",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 2,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 5,
            "product_name": "CHARMANDER SMILEY",
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "PKM001001",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/pokemon/charmander-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/pokemon/charmander-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 1,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 6,
            "product_name": "DRAGONITE HI!",
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "PKM001002",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 1,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 7,
            "product_name": "POKEMON FLYING",
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "PKM001003",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 1,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 8,
            "product_name": "PIKACHU SMILEY",
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "PKM001004",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/pokemon/pikachu-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/pokemon/pikachu-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 1,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 9,
            "product_name": "VULPIX FANCY",
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "PKM001004",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/pokemon/vulpix-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/pokemon/vulpix-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 1,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 10,
            "product_name": "BABY YODA BLUEBALL",
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Stark Warks",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "STW001001",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 3,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 11,
            "product_name": "BOBA FETT FIGHTER",
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Stark Warks",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "STW001002",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 3,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 12,
            "product_name": "LUKE SKYLWALKER & GROGU",
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Stark Warks",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "STW001003",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/star-wars/luke-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/star-wars/luke-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 3,
            "category_id": 1
        },
        {
            "product_id": 13,
            "product_name": "STORMTROOPER LIGHTSABER",
            "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Stark Warks",
            "price": 1799.99,
            "stock": 5,
            "discount": 10,
            "sku": "STW001004",
            "dues": 3,
            "image_front": "/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp",
            "image_back": "/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp",
            "create_time": "2023-12-14 18:35:18",
            "licence_id": 3,
            "category_id": 1
        }
    ]





    